https://www.bigbrandsystem.com/legalese/

Skip to content
Start HereEducationContent Profit Formula: FreeVisual Marketing Workshop: FreeOnline Business Roadmap: FreeThe BIG League: Learn MoreBooksAll BIG Brand BooksMaster Content MarketingMaster Content StrategyZero to Book PodcastFree ArticlesAll ArticlesOnline BusinessBranding & DesignAboutContactCourses Login
MenuStart HereEducationContent Profit Formula: FreeVisual Marketing Workshop: FreeOnline Business Roadmap: FreeThe BIG League: Learn MoreBooksAll BIG Brand BooksMaster Content MarketingMaster Content StrategyZero to Book PodcastFree ArticlesAll ArticlesOnline BusinessBranding & DesignAboutContactCourses LoginGeneral Disclaimer:Big Brand System is an educational and informational resource for business owners. It is not a substitute for working with a business consultant or other professional. We cannot guarantee the outcome of following the recommendations provided and any statements made regarding the potential outcome are expressions of opinion only.I make no guarantees about the information and recommendations provided herein. By continuing to use/read/participate in this website you acknowledge that we cannot guarantee any particular results, as such outcomes are based on subjective factors that are not within my control. Therefore, following any information or recommendations provided on Big Brand System are at your own risk. If you need professional help, consider hiring a business consultant.Affiliate Disclaimer:Some of the links on this site are affiliate links. This means that we may receive a commission if you click on the link and make a purchase from the affiliate. We only recommend products and services that we trust to be of high quality, whether an affiliate relationship is in place or not.I am a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for me to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.Privacy Policy:By visiting BigBrandSystem.com, you are consenting to our privacy policy.OverviewZurek Design LLC and Big Brand System is committed to protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect through this website at BigBrandSystem.com (the “Site”), and how we collect and use that information.The terms “we,” “us,” and “our” refers to Big Brand System. The terms “user,” “you,” and “your” refer to site visitors, customers, and any other users of the site.The term “personal information” is defined as information that you voluntarily provide to us that personally identifies you and/or your contact information, such as your name, phone number, and email address.Big Brand System is a blog which offers digital products for sale, and personal business coaching.Use of Big Brand System, including all materials presented herein and all online services provided by Big Brand System, is subject to the following Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all site visitors, customers, and all other users of the site. By using the Site or Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy, without modification, and acknowledge reading it.Information we collectThis Site only collects the personal information you voluntarily provide to us, which may include:Your email address and name if you choose to leave a blog comment.Your email address if you choose to subscribe to any of the free information offered here which is delivered via email.Your name, address and billing information for any purchases you make on the site.The information you provide is used to process transactions, send periodic emails, and improve the service we provide. We do share your information with trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website (such as our shopping cart software and our email marketing software), conducting our business, and servicing clients and visitors. These trusted third parties agree to keep this information confidential. Your personal information will never be shared with unrelated third parties.ActivityWe may record information relating to your use of the Site, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We use this type of information to administer the Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Site.CommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.CookiesWe may send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term “cookies” refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing the Site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Site may not work properly or at all.Third party linksThe Site may contain links to third party websites. Except as otherwise discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you on our Site. Other sites accessible through our site via links or otherwise have their own policies in regard to privacy. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third parties.SecurityWe maintain security measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, misuse, or disclosure. However, no exchange of data over the Internet can be guaranteed as 100% secure. While we make every effort to protect your personal information shared with us through our Site, you acknowledge that the personal information you voluntarily share with us through this Site could be accessed or tampered with by a third party. You agree that we are not responsible for any intercepted information shared through our Site without our knowledge or permission. Additionally, you release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of such intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.ChildrenTo access or use the Site, you must be 18 years old or older and have the requisite power and authority to enter into this Privacy Policy. Children under the age of 18 are prohibited from using the Site.Updating your informationYou may access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by contacting us via email at info (at) zurekdesign.comChanges to this policyYou acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. We will notify you of any changes to this privacy policy by posting those changes on this page.ContactIf you have questions about our privacy policy, please email us at info (at) zurekdesign.comUpdated April, 2019Pamela Wilson
Zurek Design LLC and Big Brand SystemThe BIG League is open now for online business builders! Learn more— Public enrollment closes October 15 —Get smarter! Watch free on-demand training about content marketing or visual marketing. Start HereEducationContent Profit Formula: FreeVisual Marketing Workshop: FreeOnline Business Roadmap: FreeThe BIG League: Learn MoreBooksAll BIG Brand BooksMaster Content MarketingMaster Content StrategyZero to Book PodcastFree ArticlesAll ArticlesOnline BusinessBranding & DesignAboutContactCourses Login
MenuStart HereEducationContent Profit Formula: FreeVisual Marketing Workshop: FreeOnline Business Roadmap: FreeThe BIG League: Learn MoreBooksAll BIG Brand BooksMaster Content MarketingMaster Content StrategyZero to Book PodcastFree ArticlesAll ArticlesOnline BusinessBranding & DesignAboutContactCourses Login© All rights reserved
|
Terms
Twitter
Facebook-f
Pinterest
Instagram
